(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T22:03:08.548240",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Long ago, the Heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light
A sacred law forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters
Long ago, the Heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order.
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm.
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred law forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters.
The goddess Kronii was spending her days joyfully in the heavens. A mischievous girl, today too she was chasing after her friends,
playing pranks and teasing them. She was a bit of a scatterbrained deity.
Another beautiful day... Weather like this really makes me want to sing!
せまい せまい あなぼこで
In a narrow, narrow hole,
夢を見せあう ぼくたちは
showing each other our dreams, we are...
あの世も この世も いられない
unable to stay in that world or this world.
Unable to stay in that world or this world.
ああ 神様 子どもの神様
Ah God, god of children...
ぼくらは あなたの遊んだ
We are in the sandbox where you played,
砂場の中で すり傷だらけです
covered in scrapes and scratches.
タタ タタ タタ...
Ta-ta, ta-ta, ta-ta...
踊るよ 回るよ
I'll dance, I'll spin round,
僕らの踊りはおかしな踊り
our dance is a funny dance.
踊ったつもりで 笑ったつもりで 倒れたつもりで 叫んだつもり
Thinking I danced, thinking I laughed, thinking I fell, thinking I screamed.
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ 足もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
Eyes dizzy, sound squishy, feet dizzy, illusions squishy.
太陽も月も空も神さまも 生み出して あなぐらぐらしは
Creating the sun, moon, sky, and gods, hole-dwelling...
抜け出せない 抜け出せない 抜け出せないから
Can't escape, can't escape, since we can't escape,
抜け出さない 抜け出さないから
we won't escape, since we won't escape,
お目々閉じて 2 1 0
close your eyes... 2, 1, 0!
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ あなぐらぐらしの渦の中
Falling, falling, let's keep falling into the vortex of hole-dwelling.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ いっしょに仲良くどこまでも
Falling, falling, let's keep falling, together as friends wherever we go.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじ じゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
きみと 僕とは いつまでも
You and I, forever and always,
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじ じゃないか
aren't we the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
No, no, so lonely, so lonely...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall down.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
なかま なかま あなたはいかが？
Friends, friends, how about you?
なかま なかま ぼくらはなかま
Friends, friends, we are friends.
あなたはなかま？ 合言葉？
Are you a friend? Is there a password?
あなぐら世界の合言葉？
The password for this world of holes?
抜け出せない 抜け出せない 抜け出せないから教えない
We can't escape, can't escape, so we won't tell.
あなたはなかま？ さみしいなかま？
Are you a friend? A lonely friend?
奈落に生きるなかまですか？
Are you a friend living in the abyss?
夢を かけらを 飲んでいる
Drinking up the fragments of dreams,
きみの夢も まぜまぜしていて
mixing in your dream as well.
あの世も この世も いられない
We can't be in that world or this world.
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ
Eyes are dizzy, sounds are a jumble.
腕もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
Arms are wobbly, an illusion in a jumble.
太陽も月も空も神さまも
The sun, the moon, the sky, and God...
ギトギトに 鮮やかで
So unctuously vibrant.
抜け出せない 抜け出せない 抜け出せないから抜け出さない
Can't escape, can't escape, so we won't try to escape.
抜け出さないから お目々閉じて
We won't escape, so close your eyes.
閉じて 閉じて 閉じて...
Close them, close them, close them...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall down,
あなぐらぐらしの渦の中
into the vortex of this hole-dwelling life.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall down,
一緒に仲良くどこまでも
together as friends, wherever it leads.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
きみと僕とはいつまでも
You and I, forever and ever,
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
aren't we the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall down.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
虎狼来 (Kororon)
[Title: Kororon - Lyrics, Music: Eve]
サンタマリア 起死回生の一打を放ってくれ
Santa Maria, strike a blow for a miracle comeback.
湿っぽいのはいらんな 爽快に派手にやって終い
No room for gloom, finish it bright and flashy.
その答えは自問自答の向こう側にあんだろう しょうがない
The answer must lie beyond self-questioning, it can't be helped.
アンダーグラウンドな世界の中
Inside this underground world.
井の中の蛙大会優勝者 未練たらたら
Winner of the frog-in-a-well tournament, full of lingering regrets.
SNSに夢中 自尊心なんてとうに無くなって
Obsessed with social media, self-esteem long gone.
愛を謳っては愛されたことない未体験応えよう
Singing of love, answering with an inexperienced heart that's never been loved.
毎回退場 生涯引退 生活安泰で居たい
Bowing out every time, retired for life, just wanting a peaceful life.
あんなんでもないけれど
It's nothing special, but...
描いた夢と違うけれど
It's different from the dream I envisioned, but...
なぜか心に穴があいたようだ
For some reason, it feels like there's a hole in my heart,
気づいてしまうから
because I can't help but notice it.
ありきたりな人生に
To this ordinary life,
今ピリオド打って
I'm putting an end to it now.
外れそうなこの気持ちが
This feeling that's about to derail,
抑えようもない衝動が
this uncontrollable impulse,
望み通り叶わない現実になって
becomes a reality where things don't go as wished,
まだまだくたばってなんかないぜ
I'm far from giving up yet.
神に誓ってない思い入れ
With a passion not sworn to God,
実態ない将来には宛てていたい
I want to aim for an intangible future.
騒ぐ心根を聴こう
Let's listen to the restless inner voice,
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
so it won't fade away between dreams,
足を止めていられぬよう
so we can keep moving forward.
虎狼来 甘いゴースト
Kororon, a sweet ghost,
Stay home
言葉ではなんと言える ここが正念場
You can say anything in words, this is the crucial moment.
そりゃ容赦はない 愛のないディスカッション あてにしていく
There's no mercy in a loveless discussion, relying on it.
その結果がすべてなんだ
The result is everything.
千載一遇だ まだ活かしてくれよ この世界の中
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance, let me keep living in this world.
定かではないが まだ僕の中には
It's not certain, but inside of me,
数多余すこともない事実が
there are countless undeniable facts.
虎狼に飼い慣らされるこの毎日がいや 食べられてしまい
I hate these days of being tamed by beasts, before I get devoured...
実は不安しかないけれど
To tell the truth, I feel nothing but anxiety,
描いた夢もないけれど
and I don't even have a dream envisioned,
だから心に穴があいたようだ
so it feels like there's a hole in my heart,
気づいてしまった
I've finally realized it.
ありきたりな人生に 今ピリオド打って
To this ordinary life, I'm putting an end to it now.
外れそうなこの気持ちが
This feeling that's about to derail,
抑えようもない衝動が
this uncontrollable impulse,
望み通り叶わない現実になって
becomes a reality where things don't go as wished,
まだまだくたばってなんかないぜ
I'm far from giving up yet.
神に誓ってない思い入れ
With a passion not sworn to God,
実態ない将来には宛てていたい Yeah
I want to aim for an intangible future, yeah.
騒ぐ心根を聴こう
Let me listen to the restless inner voice,
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
so it won't fade away between dreams,
足を止めていられぬよう
so I can keep moving forward,
虎狼来 甘いゴースト
Kororon, a sweet ghost,
Stay home
Yeah
Woo! Yeah!
Thank you so much for coming, everyone, to my 3D Live!
My name is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English,
...and we have Sora-senpai!
Hello! I'm Tokino Sora. Konseme~!
And Kronii, happy birthday!
Very gorgeous outfit!
Thank you! ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Yay!
Oh man, look at the stage here!
Very beautiful!
Yeah! So pretty! Look at the night sky!
きれい～！ Wow!
So pretty~! Wow!
Oh man... Whew.
Oh, Kronii, Kronii! Why did you invite me to your birthday live?
Oh, um, well, last year...
...um, we hung out together a bit,
...and I had a lot of fun, so I wanted to...
...um, invite you...
...and um, get to sing together.
I thought that would have been really great, so thank you for coming!
Oh, thank you!
Uh, I'm... So, I love you!
Oh my god, love... Love is such a strong word!
Um, I... I love you too!
I want to go to... uh... udon eating with...
I want to go eat udon with...
Yeah! Yeah, let's go eat! Oh my god!
We'll get anything! What kind of udon?
I like anything!
Yeah, I like anything.
あ、他には？
Ah, anything else?
Oh, you know, there's like cold udon, and then there's just like udon with like soup, and then there's like onsen tamago udon, I like that.
Oh, you know, there's like cold udon, and then there's just like udon with soup, and then there's like onsen tamago udon. I like that.
いろいろあるね！いろいろ、何でもいい！
There's so many varieties! Anything works!
あ、じゃあ、一緒にディナー... I'm go to dinner...
Ah, then let's go together for dinner... I'm going to dinner...
Oh, dinner? Yeah! Oh my god, that would be really good!
あっ、そういえばクロニー、ライブのハッシュタグ...
Ah, by the way, Kronii, the hashtag for the stream...
Oh yeah, I mean, if you guys haven't already checked it out, right there, #krorigin!
And yeah, I hope you guys use this hashtag. It's gonna be awesome, absolute cinema, and so yeah, keep on the lookout for Fallen Wings!
Thank you so much for coming! 本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming! Thank you so very much!
お招きいただきありがとうございました！これからは仲良くしてね！
Thank you so much for having me! Let's be good friends from now on!
Yeah! それなら嬉しいです！
Yeah! I'd be so happy with that!
大好きなフレンドだから！
Because you're a friend I love!
Oh, oh my god... so nice!
Thank you!
じゃあ、またね！ Congratulations!
Well then, see you! Congratulations!
Oh, thank you!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
A phantom flower blooming on someone's sleeve
ただ そこに藍を落とした
Simply dropping indigo dye right there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when colors gaudily dissolve
銀朱の月を添えて
Adorned with a silver-vermillion moon
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind as if rolling along
躓くごとに強くなった
Growing stronger with every stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部 抱きしめて
Embracing all the light, pain, and anger
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If you aren't chosen, then just choose
声よ轟け 夜のその向こうへ
Let your voice roar beyond the night
涙で滲んでた
It was blurred with tears
あんなに遠くの景色まで 響き渡れ
Reverberate all the way to that distant scenery
何を奏でて？ 誰に届けたくて？
What are you playing? Who do you want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's fine to stay uncertain
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the feelings are
どんなに長い葛藤も
No matter how long the struggle is
歌と散れ 残響
Scatter with the song—reverberation
ただ 一人舞う千夜
A thousand nights of dancing alone
違えない帯を結べば
If I tie an unalterable sash
派手な色も負かす様に
As if to eclipse even gaudy colors
深紅の香こそあわれ
The fragrance of crimson is truly poignant
この先どんなつらい時も
No matter how painful the times ahead may be
口先よりも胸を張って
Hold your head high rather than just speaking words
抱いた夢の灯りを全部たどるだけ
Just follow all the lights of the dreams held dear
逃げ出すため ここまで来たんじゃないだろ？
I didn't come all this way just to run away, right?
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If you aren't chosen, then just choose
声を枯らして 燃える花のように
Exhausting my voice like a burning flower
闇間を照らしたら
If I light up the darkness
曖昧すぎる正解も譜面にして
Turn even overly vague correct answers into a musical score
夜を数えて朝を描くような
Like counting the nights to paint the morning
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
Sounding a vivid tone
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regret
どんなに高い限界も
No matter how high the limit
掻き消して 残響
Erase it all—reverberation
In the heavenly realm, there is a Lake of Light that controls all worlds,
and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity.
And Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity.
As the curious Kronii continued observing,
A desire grew within her to visit not only the heavenly realm, but also the human world,
where she could talk to people and play tricks on them.
I want to go down to the human world.
I want to play some pranks. Hee-hee.
迷子 迷子 真っ只中 さあ
Lost, lost, right in the thick of it, now
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
Pa-pa-pa-ra pa-ra-noia, ah
ギコ ギコ my heart 剪定
Creak, creak, pruning my heart
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
Pa-pa-pa-ra pa-ra-noia, ah
退路 退路 断った 絡まった
Escape route, escape route, cut off, tangled up
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
Pa-pa-pa-ra pa-ra-noia, ah
サッド サッド 突っ伏して
Sad, sad, face down
パパパラ パーラ ノイド
Pa-pa-pa-ra pa-ra-noid
バ バ バグ さ バグバグ タ タ タグ 才能のタグ
Bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug! Ta-ta-tag, tag of talent!
もう ハ ハ ハグ 感情は剥ぐ 発症 苦しいは 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Already, ha-ha-hug, stripping emotions away, outbreak! "It hurts" No, no, no, no!
絶叫な感情 落下 パッパラノーイ ア
Screaming emotions falling down, pa-pa-paranoia, ah!
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
Drowning, raising a voice, spinning around and around
まじ 絶体絶命 落下 やったら滅多ら 沈め 夢 夢 嫌 嫌 嫌
Seriously desperate, falling blindly! Sink down, dreams, dreams, no, no, no!
バ バ バグ さ バグバグ
Bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug!
惑わす ズレズレ 嫌 嫌 嫌
Befuddling, out of sync, no, no, no!
バ バ バグ さ バグバグ
Bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug!
くだらない 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Worthless! No, no, no, no, no, no!
場外馬鹿騒ぎ 踊って無理 ぐるぐる せーので回れ
Out-of-bounds foolish uproar! Dancing is impossible, round and round, spin on 'Ready, go!'
場外馬鹿騒ぎ 踊って無理 ぐるぐる あんよに鎖
Out-of-bounds foolish uproar! Dancing is impossible, round and round, chains on my feet
エンドレス 闇
Endless darkness...
抱っこ 抱っこ いらない子だ
Hold me, hold me, I'm an unwanted child
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
Pa-pa-pa-ra pa-ra-noia, ah
いい子 いい子 頑張れの氾濫
Good child, good child, a flood of 'do your best'
アドミニストレーター 嗚呼
Administrator, ah...
バ バ バグ さ バグバグ
Bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug!
ランタイムバグ
Runtime bug!
反抗のバグ
Rebellious bug!
パッパバグ パッパラ パッパラノーイ ア パパラノーイ ア パパラノーイ ア 嫌 嫌 嫌
Pa-pa-bug, pa-pa-ra pa-pa-paranoia, pa-paranoia, pa-paranoia, no, no, no!
さあ 絶叫な感情 落下 パッパラノーイ ア
Now, screaming emotions falling down, pa-pa-paranoia, ah!
左 右 行き先も ぐるぐる
Left, right, destinations spinning around
悲惨 限界 脳狂っちゃって やったら滅多ら
Tragic, at the limit, mind going crazy, haphazardly!
闇 迷い 酔い いないいないばあ いないいないばあ
Darkness, lost, intoxicated, peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo!
絶叫な感情 落下 パッパラノーイ ア
Screaming emotions falling down, pa-pa-paranoia, ah!
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
Drowning, raising a voice, spinning around and around
まじ 絶体絶命 落下 やったら滅多ら
Seriously desperate, falling blindly!
凍え枯れ果て 嫌 嫌 嫌
Freezing, withering away, no, no, no!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug!
ただれ あれ あれ 嫌 嫌 嫌
Sore, stormy, stormy, no, no, no!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug!
暗れまみれ 嫌 嫌 嫌
Covered in darkness, no, no, no!
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
この世で造花より綺麗な花はないわ
There is no flower in this world more beautiful than an artificial one,
何故ならば全ては嘘で出来ている
because everything is made of lies.
アンチパシーワールド
Antipathy world.
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を穿いて
The rain of despair pierces through my umbrella,
湿らす前髪と心の内面 煩わしいわ
dampening my bangs and the back of my heart; how annoying.
いつしか言葉は疾うに枯れきって
Before I knew it, my words had long withered away,
事の実があたしに熟れている
and the fruit of truth ripens within me.
鏡に映る嘘を描いて 自らを失った絵画
Painting a lie reflected in the mirror, a painting that lost itself.
パッパッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-pa-pa-ra pa-pa-ra-ra-pa-pa
謎々数えて遊びましょう
Let's count riddles and play.
タッタッタラタッタララッタッタ
Ta-ta-ta-ra ta-ta-ra-ra-ta-ta
何故 何故 ここで踊ってるんでしょう
Why, oh why, am I dancing in this place?
簡単なことも解らないわ あたしって何だっけ
I don't even understand simple things, who was I again?
それすら夜の手に絆されて 愛のように消える
Even that is bound by the hand of night, vanishing like love.
さよう珍重 言えぬ儘泣いた フォニイ
Unable to even say goodbye, I cried, a phony.
嘘に絡まっているあたしは フォニイ
Tangled up in lies, I am a phony.
アンチパシーワールド
Antipathy world.
何時しか空の音が嫌に鳴り合って
Before I knew it, the sound of the sky was clashing unpleasantly,
色の目があなたを溶かしている
and the colorful eyes were melting you.
鏡に映る私を欠いて
Chipping away at my reflection in the mirror,
誰しもが見間違った虚像
a phantom everyone mistook.
如何して愛なんてものに群がり
Why do people flock to things like love,
それを欲して生きるのだ
and live desiring it?
今日も泳いでいる夜の電車が
Today too, the night train swims by,
通り去っていく 踊り明かせよ
passing away. Dance until dawn!
パパッパラ パッパラ ラッパッパ
Pa-pappara, pappara, rappappa...
謎々 騙して歌いましょう
Let's deceive with riddles and sing!
タタッタラ タッタラ ラッタッタ
Ta-tattara, tattara, rattatta...
何故何故 此処が痛むのでしょう
Why, oh why does this place hurt?
散々な日々は変わらないわ
The miserable days won't change.
絶望の雨は止まないわ
The rain of despair won't stop.
さよならも言えぬまま泣いた フォニイ
I cried without being able to say goodbye... Phony.
嘘に絡まっているあたしは
Entangled in lies, I am...
簡単なことも解らないわ あたしって何だっけ
I don't understand simple things... Just what was I again?
それすら夜の手にかたづされて 愛のように消える
Even that is bound by the hand of night, disappearing like love.
さよならまたねと呟いた フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
I muttered "Goodbye, see you later," phony, phony, phony.
嘘に絡まっているあたしは
Entangled in lies, I am...
造花だけが知っている秘密のフォニイ
a secret phony known only to artificial flowers.
Lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know? Do you remember, remember
how we used to be so carefree?
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice...
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time,
in every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice...
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
The goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world and cause mischief grew.
And so, she broke the rules and set foot in the Lake of Light.
The disturbance in the lake drew the attention of the heavenly guardians,
who seized Kronii and imprisoned her in a cage.
Wait, I haven't done anything yet! I was just interested in humans and just wanted to talk!
きっと手を繋ぐだけで ゾッとされる
I'm sure just holding hands will make them shudder.
馬鹿げた競争 一抜けた 通報される
If I drop out of this foolish competition, I'll be reported.
突然変異じゃない ただの僕さ
I'm not a mutation, I'm just me.
XとかYとか べき論者様は善悪多頭飼い
X or Y or whatever, the dogmatists herd their good and evil.
僕が君を「侵害」するって言いふらしてる
They keep telling everyone that I'm "infringing" on you.
Oh...
Mr. Crazy ヴィラン ヴィラン
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て
I dress differently
君の前では男子のフリする
And pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr. Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand
迎えにきて下さい
Please come pick me up
顔も知らない誰かにとって
To someone who doesn't know my face,
僕はもうヴィラン
I'm already a villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain Villain
蛇蠍ライフ
Detested life
挙句の
In the end,
糜爛
corrupting
逸脱の性をまたひた隠す
Desperately covering up my deviant nature again
雄蘂と雄蘂じゃ立ち行かないの？
Can't get anywhere with stamen and stamen?
ねぇ知ってんのか 乱歩という作家のことを Import you
Hey, do you know a writer called Ranpo? Import you
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers will bear fruit in the end
ぶるってんじゃねーよ
Don't be so afraid
多種多様の性
There are so many genders
愛しい 哀しい話をしようか
Shall we tell lovely and miserable stories?
ゼラチン質の「で？」
Gelatinous "So what?"
Oh
Mr. Crazy ヴィラン ヴィラン
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
可能性に幸あれ
All the best to your possibilities
僕のハート 1LDK
My heart is a 1LDK apartment
嫉妬くらいはさせてよ
Let me at least be jealous
Hi there モットー YOLO
Hi there, my motto is YOLO
微熱愛でいいのに
A slightly feverish love would be fine...
誰も知らない
Nobody knows
知られたくない
And I don't want them to know
皮膚の下
Under my skin
素晴らしき悪党共に捧げる唄
I devote this song to wonderful scoundrels
骨まで演じ切っちゃわれ悪辣に
Play the role to the bone, viciously
残酷な町ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The crueler the town, the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
A pop font love dancing on vulgar adverts
Oh
Mr. Crazy ヴィラン ヴィラン
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て 君の前では
I dress differently and in front of you
男子のフリを
Pretend to be a boy
拝啓 Dr. Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand
ここだよ
I'm right here
顔も知らない誰かにとって
To someone who doesn't know my face,
僕はもうヴィラン
I'm already a villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain Villain
蛇蠍ライフ 蛇蠍ライフ
Detested life, detested life
挙句の果ての糜爛
Eventually corrupting
Man...
I don't know why I'm here. I don't even deserve to be here.
I'm a goddess. I should be treated like one.
Man...
Ah, this sucks.
Go away.
La-di-da-di-da-di-da-di-da-da...
Oh, it's nice weather today!
Actually, no, I don't know if it's nice weather...
Hello?
Oh!
Oh, hello!
Hi...
Who is this beautiful blue woman?
Yeah...
In a...
Gazebo? It kind of looks like a gazebo at first, but...
Yeah, it's a gazebo.
Uh-huh.
Well-deserved for a goddess like me, if you can't tell.
Oh, yeah? Oh, you're a goddess?
Yeah, I mean, my beauty is pretty telling, so.
Aww! Well, yeah, you know, you're decent.
Decent?!
Yeah, yeah, I can see, I can see the... Yeah, I can see goddess vibes.
What?
Mhm, but...
Okay, that's a little disrespectful. I've never heard this before.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, I mean... Look who you're talking to.
Oh, okay.
Mhm.
Who... Who are you? Who do you think you are...
...to be talking...
You don't even deserve to know my name.
What?
You're in a cage!
Excuse me?!
You're like imprisoned!
No, you just said gazebo! It's not a cage, it's a gazebo!
No, it's a cage!
It's a gazebo!
If it's a gazebo, then get out of the gazebo then!
I can't!
Why can't you get out of the gazebo?
Because I'm weak... for now.
Oh, you're weak?
Yeah, I need to be protected.
Because you were bad? You did something naughty, didn't you?
No, it wasn't even that bad.
Ah, but you did do something bad.
And now you're stuck in this gazebo with the dead fly, whatever that is.
Hey!
It may look like a fly, but...
...it's... it's like my moral support...
Well, you can't talk to it like that.
Why are you talking to a dead fly?
Well, you think I have anyone else to talk to?
Oh, so you don't deny that it's a dead fly!
It's... I mean...
I mean, what are you? What are you? Like, what's that little thing on your head?
It's different from the halo on the dead fly, okay?
Look, maybe you're a fly! You have wings. What's the difference between you and that thing?
Do I look like a fly?! Yeah!
I'm not talking to you anymore. You can stay in there for eternity!
Wait, hold on! Hey, come on! Okay, maybe for a day? Hello!
Beautiful woman! Hello.
Hello, hello.
Hi!
Um, so... if you happen to open this cage, you can put it on the tab.
Do you even have money?
Uh, it can be something else. Something even more valuable.
More valuable than money?
More valuable than money.
You're not lying to me, are you?
Yeah.
And something that comes with the price of free is... guess.
My companionship!
A friend?
Maybe not a friend. I said my companionship.
Goodbye.
Hey! Hey! Come on! Okay, maybe for a day? Hello!
For a day?
For a day! For a day!
Yeah.
Now I look like a lonely ass! That's embarrassing!
Oh no, shh... It's okay. It's okay if you're lonely.
You know what, actually? I'm an angel.
Uh-huh.
We should get along.
I am feeling awfully kind right now.
Ooh! Then maybe you should!
Please beg. If you beg, I'll let you out!
Now beg.
I'm gonna speak to your higher-ups about it.
Well, you can't speak to my higher-ups if you're in this cage!
When I get out of here, you will be fired.
How are you gonna get out without me?
Do you want to take a bet? Do you want to take a gamble? Or do you want to just free me? You should just free me.
And then maybe I'll beg or whatever you want in process of my companionship.
Well, I'm here to let you out! If I don't let you out...
Hey! Just let me out!
...you're in here forever!
Just beg! It's the magic word that starts with a P!
Pray. Please! Please! Please! Please!
Finally!
Fine, because I'm so kind. Just one "please" and it would've been all over.
Okay, let's go. It's a big door!
Yeah, it is. You got this.
Okay, any day now.
It's okay. I'm an elf, I can do this for my beautiful friend, my one-day friend!
Beautiful friend, I will release thee!
Woo!
Whoa!
Oh my god, you did it!
Wow! Yay!
How did I fall there?
Why did I bother?
Yay! Woohoo! I'm free! Yeah, let's go!
Good for you.
Uh, give me your hand, please. I need to get down from here.
You can't even let yourself out. Okay.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, that's more like it, yeah.
Put you in your place.
Okay, that was really... okay. You know what, I'll let it slide because you freed me.
Yeah, that's how you show appreciation.
Yeah, well, I think we should celebrate.
Celebrate your freedom?
Yeah, yeah!
That's gonna be so good. We're gonna like...
You're gonna treat me to something, right?
I'll treat you to something afterwards.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then I'll put a good word in to your higher-ups, and then it'll be wonderful.
I don't even have higher-ups. You keep saying I have higher-ups.
You know, you never know. Life is surprising.
Really?
Yeah!
I mean, I'm sure you also have a boss, right?
Yay!
Ow! Ow!
Yay! When did you get so strong?
Ow!
I've been training recently!
Wow, it shows, yeah!
Wow, your hands are so big.
Oh, don't make it weird.
I didn't mean to.
人を過度に信じないように
So as not to trust people excessively,
愛さないように 期待しないように
so as not to love, so as not to expect anything,
かと言って角が立たないように
and yet so as not to cause friction,
気取らぬように 目立たぬように
so as not to put on airs, so as not to stand out,
誰一人傷つけぬように
so as not to hurt anyone,
虐めぬように 殺さぬように
so as not to bully, so as not to kill,
かと言って偽善がバレないように
and yet so as not to let hypocrisy show,
威張らないように
so as not to act arrogantly.
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
So as not to forget light jokes and lip service,
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
so as to always smile and scatter charm at all times.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
兎角言わずにたんとお召し上がれ
without a word, please eat your fill.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
you have to fix being a picky eater properly.
頭空っぽその後に残る心が本物なら
If the heart left after emptying your head is real,
きっと君だって同じ事
surely you are the same way.
ところで一つ伺いますが
By the way, let me ask one thing:
先日何処かで... やっぱいいや
the other day somewhere... actually, never mind.
無駄に自我を晒さぬように
So as not to expose my ego pointlessly,
話さぬように 分からぬように
so as not to speak, so as not to be understood,
でも絶対口を閉ざさぬように
but so as never to keep my mouth entirely shut,
笑わすより笑われるように
so as to be laughed at rather than to laugh at others.
人をちゃんと敬うように
So as to respect people properly,
崇めるように 称えるように
so as to worship, so as to praise,
でも決して嫌味にならないように
but so as never to sound sarcastic,
ふざけないように
so as not to mess around.
集団参加の終身刑
A life sentence of group participation,
またへーこらへーこら言っちゃって
bowing and scraping once again,
「あれっ、前髪超絶最高じゃん！」
saying "Wait, your bangs look super awesome!"
とかでーでもいいのに言っちゃって
saying stuff like that when I don't even care.
毎朝毎晩もう限界
Every morning and night, I'm at my limit.
宗教的社会の集団リンチ
Group lynching of a religious society,
でも決して発狂しないように
but so as never to go insane.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
sometimes lonely love defiles you.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
立つ鳥の後きっと糞のアート
a departing bird leaves behind art made of filth.
初めはあんな大層な大言壮語を並べたが
At first, laying out such grand and boastful talk,
嫌よ嫌よも好きのうち
playing hard to get is just liking it in disguise.
いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
My, my, but today was my first time,
こんなとはね 君センスあるよ
and to do this... you've got sense!
恋する季節に ビターチョコデコレーション
In the season of love, Bitter Choco Decoration,
恋する気持ちで ビターチョコデコレーション
with feelings of love, Bitter Choco Decoration,
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
皆が望む理想に憧れて
longing for the ideal everyone desires.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
個性や情は全部焼き払い
burning away all individuality and emotion.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
浮かぶ笑顔は殺して乳児に埋め
killing off any rising smile to bury it in infancy.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration,
僕はおとなにやっとくなったよママ
I finally became an adult, Mama.
明日もきっとこの先も
Tomorrow and surely beyond,
地獄は続く何処までも
hell will continue wherever I go.
腹からどうか今のうちは
So please, from the bottom of my heart, for now
子供の頃の気持ちのままで
with the same feelings as when I was a child,
一緒に纏わずにやっていこうぜ
let's push on without getting entangled.
あぁ思い出した
Ah, I remembered.
あったあのときの
There was, back then,
まじめそうな
that serious-looking...
やっぱいいや
actually, never mind.
I can... It's okay.
Well, I'm free now!
So I can finally get going!
Wait!
I just got out of here!
What's going on?!
Why?!
Don't just stand there, do something!
Ah, what happened?
Oh, what the heck?
Where are my... where are my beautiful clothes?
What?
Oh my god!
My... my long, luscious hair?!
What happened?
I can't...
What... what is this? I can't even take it off!
I mean... oh god, at least I still look beautiful, but like...
What happened?!
Oh man...
I don't know what's going on.
What is this place, anyway?
残機
[Song: Time Left]
しょっぱいぜ 初めて嗅いで舐めた出会い
It's salty, a meeting smelled and licked for the first time
自暴自棄です
I'm being self-destructive
平均的な正論が貧乏
Average sound arguments are poor
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome
ニンニク増しで目指した健康体
Aiming for a healthy body with extra garlic
腹歌満たしてる
Satisfying my stomach song
優等生 無知なフリして踊っちゃって
Honor student, pretending to be ignorant and dancing away
欠点です
That's a flaw
現状把握しちゃうから中断中
Pausing because I grasp the current situation
もう譲渡 見せびらかし合い 劣等感
Handing it over now, showing off, sense of inferiority
変えられやしないって分かってるからぁ？
Because I know it can't be changed, right?
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An incomprehensible player, intuitive and self-centered
求められたなら３次会
If requested, an after-after party
くだらん口喧嘩でマシになった
It got better through silly arguments
モットー？もっと？もう意外と辛いのに
Motto? More? Even though it's surprisingly tough already
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって
Even if I scream or take a hit to an annoying degree
譲れない日々よ
Unyielding days
栄養になってまた汚しあえ
Become nourishment and soil each other again
残機わかんなくて
Not knowing my remaining lives
上がんなくて
Unable to go up
脊髄反射の涙腺は
Reflexive tear ducts
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
Grateful if I sing with a muddy voice
試したいわ 暖かくて
I want to try it out, it's warm
絶体絶命な夜は気持ちいい
Desperate nights feel good
平凡な生活 夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but
先手必勝が気持ちいいな
Striking first feels so good
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
Watering plants right after returning home, human activities
実のところ恵まれても虚無感が友達
Truth is, even if blessed, a sense of emptiness is my friend
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで合図血
Whispering to stay awake, giving cues until drained dry
仲良しこよしの時間
Time to play good friends
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An incomprehensible player, intuitive and self-centered
求められたなら３次会
If requested, an after-after party
細かいご指摘も有り難い
Even detailed feedback is appreciated
結局瞳孔開いてしまうのに
Even though my pupils end up dilating in the end
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって
Even if I scream or take a hit to an annoying degree
譲れない日々よ
Unyielding days
栄養になってまた汚しあえ
Become nourishment and soil each other again
残機わかんなくて
Not knowing my remaining lives
上がんなくて
Unable to go up
脊髄反射の涙腺は
Reflexive tear ducts
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
Grateful if I sing with a muddy voice
試したいわ 暖かくて
I want to try it out, it's warm
絶体絶命な夜は気持ちいい
Desperate nights feel good
平凡な生活 夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but
先手必勝が気持ちいいな
Striking first feels so good
ただ穏やかでいたい
I just want to be peaceful
誰しも迷惑かけたくはないと思うが
I don't think anyone wants to cause trouble, but
戦わないと撫でてもらえない
If you don't fight, you won't get patted on the head
単純明快でした
It was simple and clear
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって
Even if I scream or take a hit to an annoying degree
譲れない日々よ
Unyielding days
栄養になってまた汚しあえ
Become nourishment and soil each other again
残機わかんなくて
Not knowing my remaining lives
上がんなくて
Unable to go up
脊髄反射の涙腺は
Reflexive tear ducts
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
Grateful if I sing with a muddy voice
言いたいことジャンケン ご愛嬌じゃ
Rock-paper-scissors with what we want to say, for charm
まずは時間湧くまでこしらえる
First, prepare until time arises
すぐ吐けなくて呆気なくて
Unable to spill it out right away, anticlimactic
脊髄反射の涙腺は
Reflexive tear ducts
萎ぼんだ脳で歌えて感謝です
Grateful to sing with a withered brain
ダリし痒いし薄っぺらい
Dull, itchy, and shallow
くだらないことで笑いたかった
I wanted to laugh over silly things
贖いじゃ満たされない不安感
Anxiety that atonement cannot satisfy
暴れるのは疲れるでも侮れない
Raging is exhausting, but can't be underestimated
傷にはセッションで絶頂で健康で
For wounds, a session at the peak and healthy
気持ちいいな
Feels so good
アイデンティティ
[Song: Identity]
あ、ちょっと君に伝えたい
Ah, there's something I want to tell you
何かが会ったような
Like something happened
けったい真逆の踊るベール
Strange, opposite, dancing veil
サカサマだと知って
Knowing it's upside down
好意とは魅惑のプログラム
Goodwill is a mesmerizing program
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは愛
In the end, where we arrive from here is love
アイデンティティ それは嗜好のアイデンティティ
Identity, that's an identity of preference
アイデンティティ 呻け君一人のせい
Identity, groan, it's all because of you
まだ捨てないで待って それは一つ二つのデスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, that's one or two destinies
繋げてハッピー
Connect them, happy
落ちる流れ星と歪なあの星
Falling shooting stars and that distorted star
重なる面影に寄り添う
Nestling close to the overlapping traces
そっと君に寄り添う
Gently nestling close to you
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート
A bursting field of vision, a heart jumping into the chest
光るあなたの アイデンティティ
Your glowing identity...
飛躍プライド 飛び込めデンジャラス
Flying pride, diving in dangerous,
さっと羽ばたく強気な狂気と
rapidly flapping with bold madness,
そんで裏切りお涙頂戴
and then a betrayal for crocodile tears.
ランブラララと足取りデンジャラス
Ran-bra-la-la and dangerous steps,
背後隠れた二人にフォーカス
focusing on two hidden in the background,
やっと見つけた不思議の正体
finally discovering the strange true identity.
きっと恋とは真逆のプログラム
Surely a program that's the exact opposite of love,
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは
but in the end, where we arrive from here is...
アイデンティティ それは希望のアイデンティティ
Identity, that is the identity of hope.
アイデンティティ 唸れ 君一人のせい
Identity, roar, it's all because of you alone.
まだ捨てないで待って
Don't throw it away yet, wait!
それは一つ二つのデスティニー
That's one or two destinies.
すぐさまハッピー 落ちる
Instantly happy, falling...
流れ星と歪なあの星
a shooting star and that distorted star.
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Nestling up to overlapping shadows, gently nestling up to you,
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート 刻むあなたの
bursting vision, a heart diving into the chest, engraving your...
アイデンティティ
Identity.
And now, it's time for our special guest to appear!
Um, Wada-mama, please come in!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
I was hoping to have Wada-mama appear at this year's birthday celebration...
...so I tried to reach out, and she accepted, and I'm so happy!
ちょっとお話が最初来たときは すごいびっくりしたんだけど
When I first heard about this, I was really surprised, but...
今日はすごいお誕生日の 素敵な日なので
...today is such a wonderful birthday, so...
ここに来れてとっても嬉しいです おめでとうございます！
...I'm so happy to be here. Happy birthday!
私も嬉しいです！ 来てくれてありがとうございます！
I'm so happy too! Thank you so much for coming!
And um, since we have this opportunity, can I ask Wada-mama some questions?
うん、いいよ。
Yeah, sure!
Um, like let me say... What's your favorite food?
あんこです。
Red bean paste.
And then?
あんこです。
Red bean paste.
あんこだけ。
Only red bean paste.
嘘やけど。
Just kidding though!
いっぱいあるけど あんこが一番好きです。
I have many, but red bean paste is my favorite.
Okay, I'm gonna keep that in mind for next time.
Um, in that case, oh I have one more question. What kind of game do you like?
えっとね、RPGと...
Let's see, RPGs and...
ローグライクのゲームが好きです。
I like roguelike games.
アクションは苦手。
I'm bad at action games.
ゲーマーですね！
A gamer!
でも簡単なのが好きです。
But I like easy ones.
Oh, understood!
And oh yeah, I have some exciting news to share together with Wada-mama!
And please take a look at this! Bam!
And we have so much this time too! It's gonna be so awesome!
And this illustration was drawn by none other than Wada-mama!
描きました！
I drew it!
She's so talented! Oh my god, so happy!
Was there a theme or like a particular detail you focused on for this illustration?
法被用のイラストなので ちょっと派手目に
Since it's an illustration for a happi coat, I made it a bit flashy...
でっかくみんなが楽しんで着れるような絵にしました 可愛く描けたと思います
...and big, so everyone can enjoy wearing it. I think I drew it cutely!
It's super cute! / 嬉しいです！
It's super cute! / I'm glad!
And well, let's go through the details! First, we have...
...this! Ta-da!
憧れの法被になれた！
It became the happi coat I admired!
It's the Eternal Kronie Happi, and it features a large...
design on the back,
and you can show your support!
That'd be so cool!
Woo! Yeah! Woo!
And then, uh, we have this next. Tada!
あ、可愛い！
Oh, so cute!
It's gonna be a Kronii Love! Button Badge.
缶バッジ、イエイ！イエイ！キラキラ！イエイ！
A button badge, yeah! Yeah! Sparkly! Yeah!
And it's a heart-shaped and glittery holographic—
Woah! Woah! Can badges, and it's gonna be perfect for...
...fan activities!
And you can combine it with the next product, which is...
...this one!
Yeah! It's an Oshi Bag! Yeah!
And it comes with a clear window where you can display merch,
like maybe a plushie...
...or like the can badge. So keep that in mind. Woohoo!
And then next, we have this!
あ、可愛い！イエイ！
Oh, so cute! Yeah!
Um, if you haven't seen already, it's based off of my next...
...well, not next, my outfit!
Divine Chibi Plushie Keychain!
And it's gonna be so exciting, yeah!
Yeah, cute! Yeah, yeah, yeah! あ、可愛い！ Oh!
Yeah, cute! Yeah, yeah, yeah! Oh, so cute! Oh!
And then there's a full set purchase bonus! And...
Yeah! Woo!
And the limited quantity includes original card with handwritten signature,
and then the second one is a bonus voice pack...
...called "Reminiscence".
And then, don't worry!
Even when those run out, you still get, um, other bonuses,
like original card with foil-stamped replica signature,
and then the voice pack! So don't worry!
And, yeah, once again, if you want to see the entire summary,
...here's the full set!
Yeah! Woo! Woo!
And then, if you're gonna buy, the full set is the way to go, obviously!
And that's all for Ouro Kronii's birthday! Woohoo! Yeah!
Yeah! Be sure to buy it, everyone!
And we have even more news! Woah! Take a look at this! Woohoo!
Um, so...
...the release of my first physical EP "Way2U" has been officially decided!
Sales will start right away after the stream ends,
and the album contains 5 tracks! Yeah!
And this includes "Way2U", "Storm", "I'm Human Too", "Hibiscus", and of course, the classic "Daydream".
And every song is really special, so I want everyone to listen!
And there's gonna be a CD plus an LP vinyl version, so...
...maybe you can compare them and see which one you like better!
And plus, it comes with a hand-signed poster,
um, but there's a limited amount, so be sure to check! Yeah!
And then, "Way2U" will be released as a...
...digital single on 3/15...
...which is March 15th, and distribution starts at midnight Japan time tonight!
So, don't miss it! Yeah!
And you can check the description for the sales site!
Phew, that was a mouthful!
But after this, I'd like to sing one song together with Wada-mama!
Yeah!
And I wanted to sing this song ever since I asked, so I'm really looking forward to it!
Yeah! So let's enjoy this! Yeah!
楽しみましょう！イエイ！
Let's enjoy this! Yeah!
ギラギラ
[Title: Gira Gira]
あーもう本当になんて 素晴らしき世界
Ah, what a truly wonderful world.
んで今日もまた 己の醜悪さに惑う
And today once again, I'm lost in my own ugliness.
だのに人を好きって思う気持ちだけは
Even so, the feeling of liking someone...
一丁前にあるから悶えてるんでしょう
Is fully there, and that's why I'm suffering, right?
ugly 正直言って私の顔は
Ugly... Honestly speaking, my face...
そう神様が左手で描いたみたい
Is like God drew it with His left hand.
必然この世にあるラブソングはどれひとつ
Inevitably, not a single love song in this world...
絶対私向けなんかじゃないでしょう
Is definitely meant for me, is it?
使い道のないくちづけ
Kisses with no use...
憐みを恋に
Turning pity into love...
スパンコールのかさぶたで身を守る
Protecting myself with a scab of sequin spangles...
愛されないくらいなんだ
So what if I'm not loved?
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を呑み
Glaring brightly, shining, I swallow up the night.
Rap tap tap tap 今に見ろこの luv
Rap tap tap tap, just wait and see, this love!
目に染みるは 1mgの花火
What stings my eyes is 1mg of fireworks.
Drag on drag on なんてファニー この世はビザール
Drag on, drag on, how funny, this world is so bizarre!
ギラ ギラ ギラギラ ギラ ギラ
Gira, gira! Gira-gira, gira! Gira, gira!
Unknown お釈迦様も存ぜぬうちに
Unknown... Before even the Buddha knew it...
もう健やかに狂っていたみたい
It seems I was already going madly in good health.
それは世界の方か それとも私の方ですか？
Is it the world, or is it me?
共生は端からムリでしょう
Coexistence was impossible from the start, right?
マガイモノこそかなしけれ
Counterfeits are the saddest ones of all...
無我夢中疾走る疾走る
Running wildly, sprinting, sprinting...
強い酸性雨が洗い流す前に
Before the heavy acid rain washes it away...
蛍光色の痣抱いて
I embrace my fluorescent bruise.
メラメラ火を噴いて私は夜の狼
Blazing, breathing fire, I am the wolf of the night!
Rap tap tap tap そこで見ろこの乱舞
Rap tap tap tap, watch this wild dance right there!
強くおなり あなたなりの武装で
Become strong, arm yourself in your own way!
Flap up flap up 不意に不安に
Flap up, flap up, unexpectedly into anxiety.
孤独は燃料 卑屈な町を行く
Loneliness is my fuel as I walk through this servile town.
目を閉じて もういいかい もういいかい
Closing my eyes, are you ready? Are you ready?
もしも神様が左利きなら どんなに幸せか知れない
If God were left-handed, who knows how happy I'd be?
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を呑み
Glaring brightly, shining, I swallow up the night.
Rap tap tap tap 今に見ろこの luv
Rap tap tap tap, just wait and see, this love!
目に染みるは 1mgの花火
What stings my eyes is 1mg of fireworks.
Drag on drag on なんてファニー この世はビザール
Drag on, drag on, how funny, this world is so bizarre!
ギラ ギラ ギラギラ ギラ ギラ ギラギラ ah
Gira, gira! Gira-gira, gira! Gira, gira! Gira-gira, ah!
Give love 花は満ちて
Give love, flowers bloom...
ありのまんまじゃいられない 誰の彼も
No one can stay just the way they are, not a single soul.
なんて素晴らしき世界だ
What a wonderful world this is!
ギラついてこう
Let's glare and shine on!
"This stream depicts events for dramatization and may differ from the official canon."